<?xml version="1.0" encoding="st_windows-1251"?>
<string_table>

	<!-- Jammin -->
	<string id="st_casing_pistol">
		<text>Casing, handgun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_pistol_desc">
		<text>Small brass casings with primers used to produce handgun ammunition. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_shotgun">
		<text>Casing, shotgun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_shotgun_desc">
		<text>Plastic shells with brass primers used to make shotgun ammunition. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_r5">
		<text>Casing, small rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_r5_desc">
		<text>Medium-sized brass casings with primers for intermediate rifle cartridges. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_r7">
		<text>Casing, large rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_casing_r7_desc">
		<text>Large brass casings with primers for full-sized rifle cartridges. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_pistol">
		<text>Propellant, pistol/shotgun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_pistol_desc">
		<text>Fast burning double-base propellant for use in shotguns and small handgun rounds. This variant of smokeless powder produces less overall energy than slower powders but burns more cleanly and quickly. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_rifle">
		<text>Propellant, small rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_rifle_desc">
		<text>IMR propellant for light rifle catridges and some heavy handgun cartridges. This powder burns at a medium rate and produces a good amount of energy. Cannot be used in blowback handguns and shotguns as insufficient pressures will lead to incomplete burning, causing fouling. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_mag">
		<text>Propellant, large rifle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_mag_desc">
		<text>High-yield, slow burning ball propellant for large rifle rounds. This powder produces the most energy and burns the slowest, thus it is only suitable for use in large caliber rifle ammunition fired from long-barrel weapons. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_handgun_rounds">
		<text>Handgun bullets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_handgun_rounds_desc">
		<text>Variously sized handgun rounds salvaged from ammunition. These will be useful in crafting new ammunition. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_handgun_ap_rounds">
		<text>Handgun bullets, Armor piercing</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_handgun_ap_rounds_desc">
		<text>Variously sized handgun rounds salvaged from ammunition. These have alloy penetrators embedded in the bullet. Handgun rounds are usually too slow to penetrate armor, even with penetrators, unless overpressure loads are used. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shotgun_rounds">
		<text>Lead shot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shotgun_rounds_desc">
		<text>#00 sized buckshot pellets used in hunting shotguns. These can also be melted down and cast into large slugs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shotgun_ap_rounds">
		<text>Saboted darts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shotgun_ap_rounds_desc">
		<text>Hardened steel dart rounds encased in a sabot. These are designed to be fired out of police shotguns to disable engine blocks, but do decently well against body armor. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle5_rounds">
		<text>Small caliber rifle bullets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle5_rounds_desc">
		<text>Variously sized small caliber rifle bullets used in assault rifles. Military-manufactured and covered in a full metal jacket, optimized for accuracy.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle5_ap_rounds">
		<text>Small caliber rifle bullets, Armor piercing</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle5_ap_rounds_desc">
		<text>Variously sized smallbore rifle bullets with alloy penetrators used in assault rifles. These are special-issue rounds designed to defeat armor at standard engagement ranges, but do not tumble or fragment through the body as a result. \n \n</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_rifle7_rounds">
		<text>Large caliber rifle bullets</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle7_rounds_desc">
		<text>Full-size rifle bullets covered in a metal jacket. These are commonly used to load cartridges for hunting and military sniping use. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle7_ap_rounds">
		<text>Large caliber rifle bullets, Armor piercing</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_rifle7_ap_rounds_desc">
		<text>Full-size rifle bullets with embedded alloy penetrators. These are found in special-issue cartridges used by military and special forces to defeat light vehicle armor from long range. \n \n</text>
	</string>

	
    <string id="ui_mcm_menu_ammomaker">
        <text>Ammo Maker</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_title">
        <text>Ammo Maker</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_old_salvage">
        <text>Ammo Salvage Chance</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_old_salvage_desc">
        <text>Salvage multiplier for standard ammunition. This multiplier is placed on top of individual component salvage chances. For example, if you have a 50% chance to salvage casings and this slider is set to 60%, your final chance is (0.5 * 0.6) = 0.3, or 30% chance to recover casings.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_old_salvage">
        <text>Ammo Salvage Multiplier</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_old_salvage_desc">
        <text>Salvage multiplier for standard ammunition. This multiplier is placed on top of individual component salvage chances. For example, if you have a 50% chance to salvage casings and this slider is set to 60%, your final chance is (0.5 * 0.6) = 0.3, or 30% chance to recover casings.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_new_salvage">
        <text>Good Ammo Salvage Multiplier</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_new_salvage_desc">
        <text>Salvage multiplier for fancy ammunition (assuming using Anomaly Ballistic Framework). This multiplier is placed on top of individual component salvage chances. For example, if you have a 50% chance to salvage casings and this slider is set to 60%, your final chance is (0.5 * 0.6) = 0.3, or 30% chance to recover casings.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_powder">
        <text>Propellant Salvage Chance</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_powder_desc">
        <text>Chance to recover propellant/gunpowder when disassembling ammo.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_casing">
        <text>Casing Salvage Chance</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_casing_desc">
        <text>Chance to recover casings when disassembling ammo.
        </text>
    </string>
	
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_bullet">
        <text>Bullet Salvage Chance</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mcm_ammomaker_old_salvage_desc">
        <text>Chance to recover bullets when disassembling ammo.
        </text>
    </string>
	<!-- new mats -->
	
	<string id="st_powder_fireball">
		<text>Thermal Artifact Fragments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_fireball_desc">
		<text>Pulverized remains of thermally active artifacts, for use in crafting certain types of ammo. Can be mixed into slow-burning powders to enhance their effectiveness, or be used in crafting incendiary rounds. Container is pleasantly warm to the touch.\n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_nightstar">
		<text>Volatile Artifact Fragments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_nightstar_desc">
		<text>Pulverized remains of volatile artifacts, for use in crafting certain types of ammo. Glows faintly and vibrates in the container. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_blood">
		<text>Chemical Artifact Fragments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_blood_desc">
		<text>Pulverized remains of chemically active artifacts, for use in crafting certain types of ammo. The toxic chemicals inside have been released, necessitating caution when handling. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_gravi">
		<text>Gravitational Artifact Fragments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_gravi_desc">
		<text>Pulverized remains of artifacts that exert gravitational fields, for use in crafting certain types of ammo. Constantly rattles in the container. \n \n</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_medusa">
		<text>Jellyfish Fragments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_medusa_desc">
		<text>This item has been deprecated. If you have it, sorry! Please sell this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_battery">
		<text>Electrical Artifact Fragments</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_battery_desc">
		<text>Pulverized remains of electrically active artifacts. Holding the container makes your hair stand on end. \n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_powder_fire">
		<text>Incendiary powder</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_powder_fire_desc">
		<text>Can of powder containing an incendiary mixture composed of magnesium, aluminum and barium nitrate. Usually purchased wholesale, this powder is found in small quantities in certain types of armor-piercing incendiary ammunition. Can also be synthesized from artifact fragments.\n \n </text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_crush">
		<text>crush into fragments</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batch_breakdown">
		<text>batch disassemble [!]</text>
	</string>
</string_table>